{
    "id": "521e4b29e0e94cc794f775c55c31b0f7",
    "title": "Determiners Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "There are only ......................... apples on the tree.",
            "description": "Only a few means the same as few.",
            "answers": [
                "few",
                "less",
                "a few",
                "a little"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "There aren't .............................. apples on the tree.",
            "description": "We use many before a plural noun.",
            "answers": [
                "many",
                "much",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "We don't have ............................ time to finish the work.",
            "description": "We use much before an uncountable noun.",
            "answers": [
                "much",
                "many",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I collected ................................ money than my brother.",
            "description": "We use less before an uncountable noun.",
            "answers": [
                "less",
                "few",
                "little",
                "fewer"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Now I have got ............................... problems than I used to have.",
            "description": "We use fewer before a plural noun.",
            "answers": [
                "few",
                "fewer",
                "less",
                "lesser"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I solved the problem with ............................. difficulty.",
            "description": "We use little before an uncountable noun.",
            "answers": [
                "little",
                "few",
                "lesser"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "There were ............................... people at the party.",
            "description": "We use few before a plural noun. ",
            "answers": [
                "few",
                "little",
                "less"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "There is very ............................ sugar in the jar. We should buy some.",
            "description": "We use little before an uncountable noun.",
            "answers": [
                "little",
                "less",
                "few"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "There were ................................. students than expected.",
            "description": "We use fewer before a plural noun.",
            "answers": [
                "few",
                "fewer",
                "less"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I answered ................................ questions than you.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "few",
                "fewer",
                "less"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "........................... politicians are really honest.",
            "description": "We use few before a plural noun.",
            "answers": [
                "Few",
                "Fewer",
                "Less"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I have .................................. interest in politics.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "less",
                "little",
                "lesser"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        }
    ]
}